# JONATHAN S. COOPER

1989 Grant Ave apt. 211, Ogden, UT 84401 | (385)215-4747 |

JCooper232074@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

Motivated professional with excellent interpersonal skills. General knowledge of various Windows operating system's settings and use. Familiar with various front and back end programming languages including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js and AJAX. Thrives in team-oriented environments and adapts well to the use of new software and technology. More than 3 years of technical support experience, managing software and windows environments. Over six years of experience in various other customer service settings.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### 04/2018 -Present

**Support Tech 3**, Henry Schein Practice Solutions, American Fork, UT

- Answer inbound calls, providing high level software support for Specialty Vision software.
- Make outbound phone calls to follow up with escalated customers.
- Perform system analysis, installation, and setup of new Specialty Vision software and 3rd party applications/devices for integration with the software.
- Assist callers with questions regarding functions and features of the product.

#### 01/2016-04/2018

# Support Tech 2, Henry Schein Practice Solutions, American Fork, UT

- Provide timely customer service and innovative solutions for patrons of Dentrix Core Practice Management Software.
- Periodically serve as mentor to other phone technicians for over a year since achieving Support Tech 2 designation.
- · Efficiently navigate knowledgebase resources for more complex matters
- · Implement proper troubleshooting techniques and processes for the current issue.
- · Educate callers when appropriate to avoid repeat inquiries.

#### 07/2015-12/31 /15

# Licensed Health Insurance Agent, Connexion Point, Salt Lake City, UT

- · Promptly assist clients on inbound calls with healthcare decisions.
- Research and answer questions for prospective members.
- · Enroll callers into Medicare health insurance plans.

# 03/2012-03/20 15

Veneer Dept. Operator, Milgard Windows and Doors, Tacoma, WA

- · Efficiently produce quality veneered parts to meet production needs.
- · Provide daily pass-down emails of shift performance to supervisors and management.
- Organize and lead team efforts to meet daily production quotas and maintain department order and cleanliness.

## **EDUCATION**

2015-present	IT Systems Analyst LDSBC, Salt Lake City, UT
2018	udemy.com Full Stack Developer Course
2017	treehouse.com Front End Developer Courses
2016	Test Out Windows Server Certification
2015-2015	Radiography, Salt Lake Community College, Salt Lake City, UT